<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Loris Settings Manager Blog</title>
        <link>https://sharploris.github.io/LorisSettingsManager/blog</link>
        <description>The best place to stay up-to-date with the latest Loris Settings Manager news and events.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 06:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
        <generator>Feed for Node.js</generator>
        <image>
            <title>Loris Settings Manager Blog</title>
            <url>https://sharploris.github.io/LorisSettingsManager/img/LorisLogo.png</url>
            <link>https://sharploris.github.io/LorisSettingsManager/blog</link>
        </image>
        <copyright>Copyright © 2019 Sharp Loris Games</copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Available Now!]]></title>
            <link>https://sharploris.github.io/LorisSettingsManager/blog/2019/02/21/available-now.html</link>
            <guid>https://sharploris.github.io/LorisSettingsManager/blog/2019/02/21/available-now.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>As of today, the Loris Settings Manager is approved and available on the <a href="https://assetstore.unity.com/packages/tools/utilities/loris-settings-manager-139326">Unity Asset Store</a>. I'm really glad to be able to share the last 6 months of work with my fellow developers, and I'm hoping that there are people out there who will find this useful. As I mentioned in my previous post, I have lots of improvements and additions that I'd like to make, but it's hard to be objective about their importance until other people have their hands on it, so hopefully I'll get lots of valuable feedback.</p>
]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preparing to Release]]></title>
            <link>https://sharploris.github.io/LorisSettingsManager/blog/2019/02/09/preparing-to-release.html</link>
            <guid>https://sharploris.github.io/LorisSettingsManager/blog/2019/02/09/preparing-to-release.html</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi there! Welcome to the first ever blog post about my Settings Manager. I've been working on this project for around six months now, and after spending quite some time grappling with feature creep and perfectionism, I've finally got to a place where I believe I have a minimum viable product. Now don't get me wrong, there's a ton of things I'm not quite happy with, things I'd like to improve or change, features I'd like to add or flesh out - but I believe that what I have now is enough to be really useful. I think it's pretty cool, and I figured I'd just take this opportunity to talk a little bit more about the project, how it came about, and the upcoming release.</p>
]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>